http://www.milletsfarmcentre.com/privacy-policy.html

Menu
HomeWhat's on This monthThis yearBuy ticketsWhat's here For familiesFor adultsFor schoolsFor dogsFor functions & conferencesFor foodFor weddingsShow me everythingShopping Farm ShopOnline shopFrosts Garden CentreSprouts Gift ShopPick Your OwnOther businessesEating Farmhouse KitchenFarm ShopFlower Market CafeFunctions & ConferencesGalleryPlan your visit Opening hoursGetting hereFacilitiesFAQsCoach partiesLocal infoFarm mapContact usJobsSearch
PRIVACY STATEMENT
Dear Customer
As a customer of Millets Farm Centre your privacy is extremely important to us so we’re letting you know that we’ve updated our Privacy Policy which explains how we collect, store and handle your personal data.
We collect your data because we want you to receive the best possible service from us. To help us do this we need to know information about you which helps us deliver a service, fulfil an order, personalise your communications, such as inviting you to events or keeping you up-to-date about products and promotions.
This data is collected in a number of ways, such as when you phone or email us with an enquiry, place an order, make a booking for a party or function or when you make an online purchase. Of course, we treat your data with great respect and ensure that it is secure and protected at all times.
We respect your rights regarding your personal data and we are happy for you to see what data we access, and for you to update your information or opt out at any time.
Please feel free to take a look at our Privacy Policy at any time. If you would like to unsubscribe from our database at any time please use the unsubscribe button at the bottom of our email communication.
Yours sincerely
Nigel CarterManaging Director
View our Privacy Policy here.
